Hello everyone!
I'm Rina Watanabe from Hyugaizaka46!
Today I came to Harajuku alone after school!
Yay!
I've never been to Harajuku so I'm going to have a lot of fun in Harajuku by myself.
I'm going to have a lot of fun in Harajuku by myself!
I'm off!
Bets...
I can't get enough of this food!
I made two friends.
This is really...
I'm proud of myself.
It's for sale.
It's the end of the school day.
It's the real after-school period.
I'm the kind of person who goes home right after school.
I'm the kind of person who goes home after school.
I don't really have time to go out after school like this.
I don't go out to play after school.
That's why
I'd like to invite my friends to Harajuku someday.
The place I'm heading to now is...
I've been interested in this place since I found it on SNS.
I haven't had the courage to go there.
So today, I'd like to go to a café that's been on my mind.
Today, I'd like to go to a café that's been on my mind for a long time.
There it is!
I found it!
It's so cute!
This is it.
This time I found this
Haruyoshi!
I want to go to the bakery!
It's so cute from the outside!
Amazing!
Ah, yes
And this
This ribbon motif is a famous bread store.
I'd like to wear it from here.
please?
Eh, it's so cute!
Hello, I welcome you.
Here is the menu.
Thank you very much.
Then I'll have the ribbon bread and melon soda, please.
I'd like to serve this ribbon.
Put it down.
Here.
On the wall.
There's a ribbon on the wall.
It's so cute.
I love it.
This is ribbon bread and
and a cream soda melon.
Thank you very much!
It arrived.
This time I like
This ribbon bread
It's out of focus.
Oh, here it comes.
I'll have this ribbon bread and...
And a cream melon soda
I asked for...
Hello.
This is too good to eat.
It's almost done.
So cute!
Here you go.
It's a lot of food.
What a waste!
Peach?
I think there's some kind of fruit in it.
Bon appétit!
It's so delicious!
In the bread.
In the bread
Although it's a paste
So it's really
It's more moist.
Moist and glutinous
It's so good!
Very delicious!
Yum!
Delicious!
I'm so hungry, I'm chomping down on it.
So please wait a minute.
Delicious!
Delicious.
This is actually cold.
I've been really into melon soda.
And I had been on a coffee shop tour with Miyauchi, who was in my 4th term.
We once went on a coffee shop tour together.
I think Sumire would like it too. Cute cafes like this.
I am really bad at making friends,
Recently, I often find myself alone in the classroom or between classes.
But then, there was this girl who approached me and said, “I'd like to meet you,
There was a girl who approached me.
She is really kind.
So I recently made two friends.
I was brave enough to invite them to shaved ice with me.
I succeeded in getting shaved ice after school!
I'll have the last bite!
I really haven't been to Takeshita-dori since I was a kid!
I haven't been to Takeshita-dori since I first came to Tokyo with my mother.
I only remember eating Tornado Fries with my mother when I first came to Tokyo.
I really haven't been to Takeshita-dori since two years ago, or maybe a year before that.
Oh, yes, I remember coming here to eat crepes with Rio!
I did.
I wanted to try crepes on Takeshita Street in Harajuku.
I made it come true with Rio.
This is it. We've arrived at the store, so let's go in.
This way.
I'd like to go to Pansy Potts.
I wanted to make a beaded key chain strap.
You can make a lot of different kinds of key chains.
So many that I can't even make one.
It's amazing!
Can you see it?
This...
The kind that tickles a little girl's fancy.
There are so many cute beads!
I really like to do iron beads.
I used to be addicted to iron-on beads.
I love to make them.
It's so cute!
The big heart oar is so cute!
I don't really worry about these things.
I'm not indecisive.
I'm the type of person who can decide on anything quickly.
I can do it quickly and easily.
Cute feathers!
My signature has a feather in it.
I have a feather in my signature.
Did you know that? Did you know that?
I don't know if you all know this, but my signature has a feather in it.
It's a feather motif.
I chose beads.
I'm going to put this along this U-shape now.
Wow!
What?
It's so cute!
What? Oh, my God.
That's so fun.
I'm so happy.
I'm going to recommend this to my friends.
It's fun!
It's done!
I decided on the placement of the beads.
It looks like this.
Now...
I'm going to thread the beads and make it into a strap.
I'm looking forward to it!
It's finished!
It's so cute, this big frost!
I'm proud of myself, but it looks like it's ready for sale.
I only threaded the beads, but I'm very happy with how cute it turned out.
I just threaded the beads, but I'm really happy with how cute it turned out. There's one more place I want to go, so I'm on my way there now.
I'm heading there because there's one more place I want to go, and it's related to something I really enjoy doing.
It's a place where you can send gifts.
I would like to make it for the person to whom I would like to send it.
I'd like to make it for them as well.
I'm going to head over to the store in the express cloud.
I would like to head to the shop inside the Express Cloud now!
There are a lot of cute and colorful flowers lined up here.
Here, I'd like to choose flowers for myself and for the person I'd like to give a gift to.
I wonder if there are any flowers that interest me, or if they are cute...
What do you think?
I thought these deep flowers were really cute.
Gabelins.
They're pretty, aren't they?
It's cute.
It's so cute.
I thought this little blue one was cute.
These are dyed flowers.
Wow!
There are so many different kinds.
There are 54 kinds on display right now.
Wow.
That's right.
They're all lined up.
There are indeed a lot of varieties.
And the colors...
It sure is pretty.
Thank you.
It's so cute.
The yellow color is certainly summery.
I'd like to have these three.
Thank you very much.
I chose the flowers I want to decorate my house with.
I'd like to make the flowers I want to give as a gift, too.
I'd like to give them to my senior, Mr. Sunao Kosaka.
I have a lot of things to thank him for.
I have many things to thank him for.
I would like to give him flowers as a gift to express my gratitude.
I have an image of this person as a very elegant person with a quiet atmosphere.
I'd like to collect purple and light colors.
This is also dyed.
It's really beautiful.
Cute!
And the other one...
The color of the skin.
It's quite mature.
I'm sure.
It all comes out at once.
Yes, it does.
Certainly more mature.
Cute.
It's pretty much the image of the person I want to send.
I'd like to send.
It's a side flower.
I think it's also possible to put the small white flower here.
Is that possible?
Yes, it's possible.
Pretty.
Might be nice.
It's cute.
It's nice.
Then this way, please.
Yes, these four, please.
Thank you.
This is a message card based on the Nutrition Facts table.
It says here what percentage.
You choose your own words here.
I'd like to write while choosing this reference material.
What should I do?
This way.
There are so many things I want to draw.
Beauty, Respect, Ispect, Beauty...
I finished it!
First of all
Beauty
and Ispect
And Kindness
So far everything is 1000%.
And 50% because I thought she was probably a little clumsy.
And finally, 1000% nerdiness.
This is because I think he's probably the same type of person as me.
I'll just increase the nerdiness.
That's it. That's it.
Yes, sir.
I'd like to present it to you. Wait a minute.
So this time, we walked around Harajuku a lot, and had a lot of fun
At the end, I got some cute flowers, so I'm very happy.
So I'm waiting for your channel subscriptions and comments!
I hope you all enjoy the show. See you soon!
How cute!
So cute! So beautiful! It's a little purplish!
It's super beautiful!
What?
I'm a nerd.
Before that...
What's this?
50%?
What does that mean? This.
It means he's a coward.
Is it obvious?
I'm the one who's timid with Rina-chan.
Thank you, Rina-chan.
I'll be sure to put it up in my house.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.